[
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 11 and height 10?",
      "correctAnswer": "55.0",
      "options": [
        "55.0",
        "57.5",
        "52.5",
        "59.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 30 and height 15?",
      "correctAnswer": "225.0",
      "options": [
        "229.0",
        "222.5",
        "227.5",
        "225.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 6 and height 4?",
      "correctAnswer": "12.0",
      "options": [
        "14.5",
        "9.5",
        "16.0",
        "12.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 36 and height 12?",
      "correctAnswer": "216.0",
      "options": [
        "213.5",
        "218.5",
        "216.0",
        "220.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 27 and height 29?",
      "correctAnswer": "391.5",
      "options": [
        "394.0",
        "389.0",
        "395.5",
        "391.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 4 and height 39?",
      "correctAnswer": "78.0",
      "options": [
        "78.0",
        "82.0",
        "75.5",
        "80.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 11 and height 23?",
      "correctAnswer": "126.5",
      "options": [
        "126.5",
        "129.0",
        "130.5",
        "124.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 23 and height 10?",
      "correctAnswer": "115.0",
      "options": [
        "117.5",
        "112.5",
        "119.0",
        "115.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 32 and height 32?",
      "correctAnswer": "512.0",
      "options": [
        "516.0",
        "509.5",
        "514.5",
        "512.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a triangle with<br> base 37 and height 39?",
      "correctAnswer": "721.5",
      "options": [
        "719.0",
        "724.0",
        "725.5",
        "721.5"
      ]
    }
]